{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222868200","data":{"timestamp":" 947222868200"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222870619","data":{"timestamp":" 947222870618"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222871060","data":{"timestamp":" 947222871060"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222871261","data":{"timestamp":" 947222871260"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222871775","data":{"timestamp":" 947222871775"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222874669","data":{"timestamp":" 947222874668"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASUBIRI"," userResponse":" NINASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222875254","data":{"timestamp":" 947222875254"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222875448","data":{"timestamp":" 947222875447"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222876213","data":{"timestamp":" 947222876213"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222878835","data":{"timestamp":" 947222878834"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222879630","data":{"timestamp":" 947222879629"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222882591","data":{"timestamp":" 947222882590"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222883831","data":{"timestamp":" 947222883831"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" NIMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222884275","data":{"timestamp":" 947222884274"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222885037","data":{"timestamp":" 947222885037"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" MSTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222887635","data":{"timestamp":" 947222887634"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222889095","data":{"timestamp":" 947222889095"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIIMBIA"," userResponse":" ANANIIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222889553","data":{"timestamp":" 947222889553"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222891947","data":{"timestamp":" 947222891947"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222892302","data":{"timestamp":" 947222892302"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222893255","data":{"timestamp":" 947222893255"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222893738","data":{"timestamp":" 947222893738"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222894611","data":{"timestamp":" 947222894611"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUONI"," userResponse":" HUONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222897524","data":{"timestamp":" 947222897524"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TWASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222898377","data":{"timestamp":" 947222898376"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222899049","data":{"timestamp":" 947222899049"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222900133","data":{"timestamp":" 947222900133"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222903360","data":{"timestamp":" 947222903359"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222903840","data":{"timestamp":" 947222903840"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYE"," userResponse":" ALIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222904455","data":{"timestamp":" 947222904455"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222905034","data":{"timestamp":" 947222905033"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222906360","data":{"timestamp":" 947222906359"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" ANAWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222906756","data":{"timestamp":" 947222906755"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222907465","data":{"timestamp":" 947222907464"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222910104","data":{"timestamp":" 947222910103"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATAGA"," userResponse":" WATATAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222910886","data":{"timestamp":" 947222910886"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYAI"," userResponse":" MAYAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222911499","data":{"timestamp":" 947222911499"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222911842","data":{"timestamp":" 947222911842"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALE"," userResponse":" ALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222915305","data":{"timestamp":" 947222915304"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222916012","data":{"timestamp":" 947222916011"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222917134","data":{"timestamp":" 947222917133"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANARUDI"," userResponse":" WANARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222917907","data":{"timestamp":" 947222917907"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222918466","data":{"timestamp":" 947222918464"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222921812","data":{"timestamp":" 947222921812"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" WANATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222924649","data":{"timestamp":" 947222924648"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWASIKIA"," userResponse":" NAWASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222925434","data":{"timestamp":" 947222925434"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIIMBA"," userResponse":" WAKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222926360","data":{"timestamp":" 947222926359"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222927183","data":{"timestamp":" 947222927182"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222927689","data":{"timestamp":" 947222927689"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIWE"," userResponse":" USIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222927987","data":{"timestamp":" 947222927986"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222929136","data":{"timestamp":" 947222929135"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222931870","data":{"timestamp":" 947222931870"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222932212","data":{"timestamp":" 947222932212"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAJA"," userResponse":" YAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222932479","data":{"timestamp":" 947222932479"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222933474","data":{"timestamp":" 947222933474"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222936945","data":{"timestamp":" 947222936944"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222937801","data":{"timestamp":" 947222937801"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPITA"," userResponse":" ANAPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222938796","data":{"timestamp":" 947222938796"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222941090","data":{"timestamp":" 947222941088"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUKO"," userResponse":" YUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222941961","data":{"timestamp":" 947222941961"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHIFU"," userResponse":" NADHIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222942765","data":{"timestamp":" 947222942764"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222945238","data":{"timestamp":" 947222945238"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222945705","data":{"timestamp":" 947222945704"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKE"," userResponse":" VYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222945981","data":{"timestamp":" 947222945981"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222946637","data":{"timestamp":" 947222946636"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222947086","data":{"timestamp":" 947222947086"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222949791","data":{"timestamp":" 947222949790"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINAENDA"," userResponse":" VINAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222950777","data":{"timestamp":" 947222950777"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222951332","data":{"timestamp":" 947222951332"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222951806","data":{"timestamp":" 947222951806"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222954350","data":{"timestamp":" 947222954349"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222954812","data":{"timestamp":" 947222954812"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222955208","data":{"timestamp":" 947222955208"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222958438","data":{"timestamp":" 947222958437"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOTEMBEA"," userResponse":" ANAPOTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222961700","data":{"timestamp":" 947222961700"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222962323","data":{"timestamp":" 947222962322"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222963265","data":{"timestamp":" 947222963265"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAUZA"," userResponse":" ANAUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222964058","data":{"timestamp":" 947222964058"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" VINYWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222964820","data":{"timestamp":" 947222964819"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222967616","data":{"timestamp":" 947222967615"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAPENDA"," userResponse":" NAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222968485","data":{"timestamp":" 947222968484"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" VINYWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222969382","data":{"timestamp":" 947222969381"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222971637","data":{"timestamp":" 947222971636"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222972450","data":{"timestamp":" 947222972450"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222972734","data":{"timestamp":" 947222972734"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222973567","data":{"timestamp":" 947222973567"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222974390","data":{"timestamp":" 947222974390"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222976540","data":{"timestamp":" 947222976539"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222978063","data":{"timestamp":" 947222978063"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAVIPENDA"," userResponse":" UNAVIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222981252","data":{"timestamp":" 947222981252"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222983730","data":{"timestamp":" 947222983729"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222984711","data":{"timestamp":" 947222984710"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222985733","data":{"timestamp":" 947222985733"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAPELEKA"," userResponse":" WANAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222986322","data":{"timestamp":" 947222986321"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222986917","data":{"timestamp":" 947222986916"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAO"," userResponse":" CHAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222987169","data":{"timestamp":" 947222987169"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222988058","data":{"timestamp":" 947222988058"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222989197","data":{"timestamp":" 947222989197"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222990015","data":{"timestamp":" 947222990015"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWANI"," userResponse":" VICHWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222990560","data":{"timestamp":" 947222990560"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAO"," userResponse":" MWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222992530","data":{"timestamp":" 947222992529"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222993182","data":{"timestamp":" 947222993182"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222993929","data":{"timestamp":" 947222993928"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEREVU"," userResponse":" WEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222997208","data":{"timestamp":" 947222997208"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222997921","data":{"timestamp":" 947222997921"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222998914","data":{"timestamp":" 947222998914"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASUKWA"," userResponse":" ANASUKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222999304","data":{"timestamp":" 947222999303"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947222999841","data":{"timestamp":" 947222999841"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223002619","data":{"timestamp":" 947223002619"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAENDA"," userResponse":" ATAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223003149","data":{"timestamp":" 947223003148"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223003392","data":{"timestamp":" 947223003391"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223004188","data":{"timestamp":" 947223004188"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223004775","data":{"timestamp":" 947223004774"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223005528","data":{"timestamp":" 947223005528"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223006152","data":{"timestamp":" 947223006152"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223009243","data":{"timestamp":" 947223009243"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMECHOKA"," userResponse":" NIMECHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223009866","data":{"timestamp":" 947223009866"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223010427","data":{"timestamp":" 947223010427"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223010503","data":{"timestamp":" 947223010502"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e00943c7-2742-4f20-a6ac-94d63be663ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223078328","data":{"timestamp":" 947223078328"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223080704","data":{"timestamp":" 947223080704"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223081137","data":{"timestamp":" 947223081137"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223081330","data":{"timestamp":" 947223081330"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223081837","data":{"timestamp":" 947223081837"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223084696","data":{"timestamp":" 947223084696"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASUBIRI"," userResponse":" NINASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223085270","data":{"timestamp":" 947223085269"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223085453","data":{"timestamp":" 947223085453"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223086206","data":{"timestamp":" 947223086206"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninasubiri teksi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223088809","data":{"timestamp":" 947223088809"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAENDA"," userResponse":" TUNAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223089581","data":{"timestamp":" 947223089581"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tunaenda nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223092476","data":{"timestamp":" 947223092476"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223093689","data":{"timestamp":" 947223093689"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMESIMAMA"," userResponse":" NIMESIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223094122","data":{"timestamp":" 947223094122"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223094888","data":{"timestamp":" 947223094887"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSTARI"," userResponse":" MSTARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223097467","data":{"timestamp":" 947223097467"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223098910","data":{"timestamp":" 947223098910"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIIMBIA"," userResponse":" ANANIIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223099354","data":{"timestamp":" 947223099353"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu ananiimbia wimbo."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223101692","data":{"timestamp":" 947223101692"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223102045","data":{"timestamp":" 947223102045"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223103015","data":{"timestamp":" 947223103015"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223103507","data":{"timestamp":" 947223103506"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223104398","data":{"timestamp":" 947223104398"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUONI"," userResponse":" HUONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223107243","data":{"timestamp":" 947223107243"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TWASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223108116","data":{"timestamp":" 947223108115"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223108789","data":{"timestamp":" 947223108789"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223109876","data":{"timestamp":" 947223109875"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Twasubiri Nanu na mimi!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223113152","data":{"timestamp":" 947223113150"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223113634","data":{"timestamp":" 947223113634"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYE"," userResponse":" ALIYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223114247","data":{"timestamp":" 947223114247"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223114818","data":{"timestamp":" 947223114817"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMI"," userResponse":" NAMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223116148","data":{"timestamp":" 947223116147"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWAPELEKA"," userResponse":" ANAWAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223116539","data":{"timestamp":" 947223116539"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223117251","data":{"timestamp":" 947223117250"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke aliye karibu nami anawapeleka kuku nyumbani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223119868","data":{"timestamp":" 947223119867"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATAGA"," userResponse":" WATATAGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223120663","data":{"timestamp":" 947223120662"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYAI"," userResponse":" MAYAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223121296","data":{"timestamp":" 947223121295"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223121653","data":{"timestamp":" 947223121653"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watataga mayai ili ale."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALE"," userResponse":" ALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223125158","data":{"timestamp":" 947223125158"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAUME"," userResponse":" WANAUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223125850","data":{"timestamp":" 947223125849"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223126984","data":{"timestamp":" 947223126984"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANARUDI"," userResponse":" WANARUDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223127754","data":{"timestamp":" 947223127753"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223128311","data":{"timestamp":" 947223128311"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223131725","data":{"timestamp":" 947223131724"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" WANATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223134635","data":{"timestamp":" 947223134635"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWASIKIA"," userResponse":" NAWASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223135422","data":{"timestamp":" 947223135421"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIIMBA"," userResponse":" WAKIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223136348","data":{"timestamp":" 947223136347"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANU"," userResponse":" NANU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223137165","data":{"timestamp":" 947223137165"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MDOGO"," userResponse":" MDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223137671","data":{"timestamp":" 947223137670"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIWE"," userResponse":" USIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223137971","data":{"timestamp":" 947223137970"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223139104","data":{"timestamp":" 947223139104"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WASIWASI"," userResponse":" WASIWASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223141800","data":{"timestamp":" 947223141799"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223142137","data":{"timestamp":" 947223142136"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAJA"," userResponse":" YAJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223142402","data":{"timestamp":" 947223142402"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223143399","data":{"timestamp":" 947223143399"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Teksi yaja kwa haraka."," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223146890","data":{"timestamp":" 947223146889"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223147754","data":{"timestamp":" 947223147754"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPITA"," userResponse":" ANAPITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223148750","data":{"timestamp":" 947223148749"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223151048","data":{"timestamp":" 947223151048"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUKO"," userResponse":" YUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223151924","data":{"timestamp":" 947223151924"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHIFU"," userResponse":" NADHIFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223152727","data":{"timestamp":" 947223152726"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223155174","data":{"timestamp":" 947223155173"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223155636","data":{"timestamp":" 947223155636"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKE"," userResponse":" VYAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223155916","data":{"timestamp":" 947223155915"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223156568","data":{"timestamp":" 947223156568"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIZURI"," userResponse":" VIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223157020","data":{"timestamp":" 947223157020"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu vyake si vizuri kweli?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWELI"," userResponse":" KWELI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223159743","data":{"timestamp":" 947223159742"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINAENDA"," userResponse":" VINAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223160733","data":{"timestamp":" 947223160733"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223161261","data":{"timestamp":" 947223161260"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223161737","data":{"timestamp":" 947223161736"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223164309","data":{"timestamp":" 947223164308"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223164770","data":{"timestamp":" 947223164770"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223165163","data":{"timestamp":" 947223165162"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CLICK"," userResponse":" CLICK"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223168413","data":{"timestamp":" 947223168412"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" anapotembea."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPOTEMBEA"," userResponse":" ANAPOTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223171720","data":{"timestamp":" 947223171718"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMME"," userResponse":" MWANAMME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223172365","data":{"timestamp":" 947223172364"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223173320","data":{"timestamp":" 947223173320"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAUZA"," userResponse":" ANAUZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223174124","data":{"timestamp":" 947223174124"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" VINYWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223174887","data":{"timestamp":" 947223174887"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223177640","data":{"timestamp":" 947223177640"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAPENDA"," userResponse":" NAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223178508","data":{"timestamp":" 947223178506"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINYWAJI"," userResponse":" VINYWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223179410","data":{"timestamp":" 947223179409"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223181726","data":{"timestamp":" 947223181726"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223182555","data":{"timestamp":" 947223182554"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223182846","data":{"timestamp":" 947223182845"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223183692","data":{"timestamp":" 947223183692"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223184530","data":{"timestamp":" 947223184530"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223186664","data":{"timestamp":" 947223186663"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223188190","data":{"timestamp":" 947223188189"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unavipenda?"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAVIPENDA"," userResponse":" UNAVIPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223191361","data":{"timestamp":" 947223191361"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223193793","data":{"timestamp":" 947223193792"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223194772","data":{"timestamp":" 947223194771"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAWAKE"," userResponse":" WANAWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223195785","data":{"timestamp":" 947223195785"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAPELEKA"," userResponse":" WANAPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223196374","data":{"timestamp":" 947223196373"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223196972","data":{"timestamp":" 947223196972"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAO"," userResponse":" CHAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223197228","data":{"timestamp":" 947223197228"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223198113","data":{"timestamp":" 947223198113"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIONI"," userResponse":" JIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223199253","data":{"timestamp":" 947223199252"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223200068","data":{"timestamp":" 947223200068"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VICHWANI"," userResponse":" VICHWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223200616","data":{"timestamp":" 947223200615"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAO"," userResponse":" MWAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223202615","data":{"timestamp":" 947223202615"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223203271","data":{"timestamp":" 947223203270"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223204027","data":{"timestamp":" 947223204026"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je si werevu?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEREVU"," userResponse":" WEREVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223207265","data":{"timestamp":" 947223207264"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223207993","data":{"timestamp":" 947223207993"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223209001","data":{"timestamp":" 947223209000"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASUKWA"," userResponse":" ANASUKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223209392","data":{"timestamp":" 947223209392"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYWELE"," userResponse":" NYWELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223209934","data":{"timestamp":" 947223209933"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223212659","data":{"timestamp":" 947223212658"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAENDA"," userResponse":" ATAENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223213193","data":{"timestamp":" 947223213192"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJE"," userResponse":" NJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223213444","data":{"timestamp":" 947223213444"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223214240","data":{"timestamp":" 947223214240"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223214825","data":{"timestamp":" 947223214825"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223215582","data":{"timestamp":" 947223215581"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223216218","data":{"timestamp":" 947223216217"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ataenda nje na marafiki zake leo usiku."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223219391","data":{"timestamp":" 947223219390"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMECHOKA"," userResponse":" NIMECHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223220021","data":{"timestamp":" 947223220020"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223222727","data":{"timestamp":" 947223222726"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223223687","data":{"timestamp":" 947223223687"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANANIWEKA"," userResponse":" ANANIWEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223224489","data":{"timestamp":" 947223224488"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MGONGONI"," userResponse":" MGONGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223225060","data":{"timestamp":" 947223225060"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAKE"," userResponse":" KWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223226768","data":{"timestamp":" 947223226767"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKAPUMZIKE"," userResponse":" NIKAPUMZIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223229817","data":{"timestamp":" 947223229817"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAIMBA"," userResponse":" ANAIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223231083","data":{"timestamp":" 947223231082"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223231519","data":{"timestamp":" 947223231519"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223232347","data":{"timestamp":" 947223232346"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223233977","data":{"timestamp":" 947223233976"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USICHELEWE"," userResponse":" USICHELEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223235020","data":{"timestamp":" 947223235019"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GOGO"," userResponse":" GOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223236108","data":{"timestamp":" 947223236108"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASUBIRI"," userResponse":" ANASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223236606","data":{"timestamp":" 947223236605"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223237118","data":{"timestamp":" 947223237117"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGO"," userResponse":" LANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223238060","data":{"timestamp":" 947223238060"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaimba Tafadhali Bwana Teksi usichelewe Gogo anasubiri kwenye lango kuu."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223240807","data":{"timestamp":" 947223240806"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNA"," userResponse":" KUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223241471","data":{"timestamp":" 947223241471"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223242072","data":{"timestamp":" 947223242071"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223242333","data":{"timestamp":" 947223242333"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMI"," userResponse":" TUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223245354","data":{"timestamp":" 947223245353"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYE"," userResponse":" YEYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223245677","data":{"timestamp":" 947223245677"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223246650","data":{"timestamp":" 947223246649"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" ANAPUMZIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223249430","data":{"timestamp":" 947223249428"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUTAKUWA"," userResponse":" TUTAKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223250193","data":{"timestamp":" 947223250192"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223250635","data":{"timestamp":" 947223250635"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223251408","data":{"timestamp":" 947223251407"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tutakuwa nyumbani hivi karibuni."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBUNI"," userResponse":" KARIBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223254434","data":{"timestamp":" 947223254434"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223254809","data":{"timestamp":" 947223254809"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223255630","data":{"timestamp":" 947223255629"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDEGE"," userResponse":" NDEGE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223256565","data":{"timestamp":" 947223256564"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANARUKA"," userResponse":" WANARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223257513","data":{"timestamp":" 947223257513"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223258334","data":{"timestamp":" 947223258333"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223261344","data":{"timestamp":" 947223261343"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAZIMA"," userResponse":" LAZIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223261989","data":{"timestamp":" 947223261987"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAFIKE"," userResponse":" WAFIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223262836","data":{"timestamp":" 947223262836"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223263499","data":{"timestamp":" 947223263499"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223263957","data":{"timestamp":" 947223263956"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GIZA"," userResponse":" GIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223264767","data":{"timestamp":" 947223264766"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lazima wafike nyumbani kabla giza kuingia."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUINGIA"," userResponse":" KUINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223268049","data":{"timestamp":" 947223268047"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAMKE"," userResponse":" MWANAMKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223268587","data":{"timestamp":" 947223268586"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223269168","data":{"timestamp":" 947223269168"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223269835","data":{"timestamp":" 947223269834"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPULI"," userResponse":" VIPULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223271197","data":{"timestamp":" 947223271197"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanamke huyu ana vipuli maridadi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIDADI"," userResponse":" MARIDADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223273913","data":{"timestamp":" 947223273912"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani alivinunua mjini leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223275203","data":{"timestamp":" 947223275202"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani alivinunua mjini leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIVINUNUA"," userResponse":" ALIVINUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223276200","data":{"timestamp":" 947223276199"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani alivinunua mjini leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJINI"," userResponse":" MJINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223276539","data":{"timestamp":" 947223276538"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani alivinunua mjini leo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223278840","data":{"timestamp":" 947223278839"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKIWA"," userResponse":" NIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223279536","data":{"timestamp":" 947223279535"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223280726","data":{"timestamp":" 947223280726"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NITANUNUA"," userResponse":" NITANUNUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223281388","data":{"timestamp":" 947223281387"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPULI"," userResponse":" VIPULI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223282228","data":{"timestamp":" 947223282227"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINGI"," userResponse":" VINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223283104","data":{"timestamp":" 947223283103"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYANGU"," userResponse":" VYANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223283405","data":{"timestamp":" 947223283404"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223283666","data":{"timestamp":" 947223283665"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYA"," userResponse":" VYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223284384","data":{"timestamp":" 947223284383"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nikiwa mkubwa nitanunua vipuli vingi vyangu na vya mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223287652","data":{"timestamp":" 947223287652"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu anaanza kuchoka sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223288490","data":{"timestamp":" 947223288489"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu anaanza kuchoka sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAANZA"," userResponse":" ANAANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223289173","data":{"timestamp":" 947223289173"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu anaanza kuchoka sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHOKA"," userResponse":" KUCHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223289786","data":{"timestamp":" 947223289786"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamangu anaanza kuchoka sasa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223293022","data":{"timestamp":" 947223293021"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAMWIMBIA"," userResponse":" NAMWIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223293569","data":{"timestamp":" 947223293568"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WIMBO"," userResponse":" WIMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223294673","data":{"timestamp":" 947223294673"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223295149","data":{"timestamp":" 947223295149"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWANA"," userResponse":" BWANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223296088","data":{"timestamp":" 947223296088"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223297506","data":{"timestamp":" 947223297505"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKUJA"," userResponse":" UNAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223299352","data":{"timestamp":" 947223299351"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNASUBIRI"," userResponse":" TUNASUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223299946","data":{"timestamp":" 947223299945"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223300179","data":{"timestamp":" 947223300179"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223301136","data":{"timestamp":" 947223301135"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Namwimbia wimbo Tafadhali Bwana Teksi unakuja tunasubiri mimi na mamangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223304068","data":{"timestamp":" 947223304068"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGOJA"," userResponse":" NGOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223307279","data":{"timestamp":" 947223307277"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINASIKIA"," userResponse":" NINASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223307844","data":{"timestamp":" 947223307844"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223310478","data":{"timestamp":" 947223310477"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVI"," userResponse":" HIVI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223311071","data":{"timestamp":" 947223311071"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223312099","data":{"timestamp":" 947223312099"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hivi hapa inakuja!!!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAKUJA"," userResponse":" INAKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223315103","data":{"timestamp":" 947223315103"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223315319","data":{"timestamp":" 947223315318"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223315924","data":{"timestamp":" 947223315923"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEKSI"," userResponse":" TEKSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223316161","data":{"timestamp":" 947223316161"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YETU"," userResponse":" YETU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223316809","data":{"timestamp":" 947223316808"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUBWA"," userResponse":" KUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223317611","data":{"timestamp":" 947223317610"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223320559","data":{"timestamp":" 947223320559"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMEKUJA"," userResponse":" IMEKUJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223321641","data":{"timestamp":" 947223321641"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNIPELEKA"," userResponse":" KUNIPELEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223322407","data":{"timestamp":" 947223322407"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIMI"," userResponse":" MIMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223322628","data":{"timestamp":" 947223322627"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223323431","data":{"timestamp":" 947223323431"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMANGU"," userResponse":" MAMANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223324349","data":{"timestamp":" 947223324347"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223328150","data":{"timestamp":" 947223328149"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" NIMEFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223329404","data":{"timestamp":" 947223329404"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimefurahi sana!"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223333509","data":{"timestamp":" 947223333508"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223336260","data":{"timestamp":" 947223336259"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223336383","data":{"timestamp":" 947223336382"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAHERI"," userResponse":" KWAHERI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223343918","data":{"timestamp":" 947223343917"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223352856","data":{"timestamp":" 947223352856"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ef91835b-07b1-44c2-8602-7984ae33f67b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_39"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwaheri!!!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223362023","data":{"timestamp":" 947223362021"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223364185","data":{"timestamp":" 947223364184"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223366325","data":{"timestamp":" 947223366323"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223369532","data":{"timestamp":" 947223369531"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223371765","data":{"timestamp":" 947223371764"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223374016","data":{"timestamp":" 947223374016"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223376825","data":{"timestamp":" 947223376825"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223378993","data":{"timestamp":" 947223378993"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223381195","data":{"timestamp":" 947223381193"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223384468","data":{"timestamp":" 947223384468"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223386519","data":{"timestamp":" 947223386519"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223388552","data":{"timestamp":" 947223388552"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223391450","data":{"timestamp":" 947223391450"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223393638","data":{"timestamp":" 947223393638"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223395861","data":{"timestamp":" 947223395860"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223398918","data":{"timestamp":" 947223398918"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223401259","data":{"timestamp":" 947223401259"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223403632","data":{"timestamp":" 947223403632"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223406690","data":{"timestamp":" 947223406689"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223408864","data":{"timestamp":" 947223408863"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223411026","data":{"timestamp":" 947223411025"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223414151","data":{"timestamp":" 947223414151"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223416357","data":{"timestamp":" 947223416356"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223418532","data":{"timestamp":" 947223418531"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223421702","data":{"timestamp":" 947223421701"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223424168","data":{"timestamp":" 947223424168"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223426618","data":{"timestamp":" 947223426617"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223429777","data":{"timestamp":" 947223429777"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223432079","data":{"timestamp":" 947223432079"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223434431","data":{"timestamp":" 947223434431"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223437442","data":{"timestamp":" 947223437442"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223439660","data":{"timestamp":" 947223439660"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223441859","data":{"timestamp":" 947223441858"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223444847","data":{"timestamp":" 947223444846"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223447233","data":{"timestamp":" 947223447233"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223449638","data":{"timestamp":" 947223449638"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223452772","data":{"timestamp":" 947223452771"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223455176","data":{"timestamp":" 947223455175"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223457583","data":{"timestamp":" 947223457582"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223460569","data":{"timestamp":" 947223460569"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223462864","data":{"timestamp":" 947223462864"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223465089","data":{"timestamp":" 947223465088"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223468355","data":{"timestamp":" 947223468354"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223470655","data":{"timestamp":" 947223470655"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223472920","data":{"timestamp":" 947223472919"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223476339","data":{"timestamp":" 947223476339"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223478806","data":{"timestamp":" 947223478806"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223481262","data":{"timestamp":" 947223481261"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223484174","data":{"timestamp":" 947223484174"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223486356","data":{"timestamp":" 947223486355"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223488533","data":{"timestamp":" 947223488533"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223491950","data":{"timestamp":" 947223491948"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223494288","data":{"timestamp":" 947223494288"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223496644","data":{"timestamp":" 947223496643"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223499771","data":{"timestamp":" 947223499770"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223502042","data":{"timestamp":" 947223502041"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223504318","data":{"timestamp":" 947223504318"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223507410","data":{"timestamp":" 947223507410"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223509567","data":{"timestamp":" 947223509566"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223511714","data":{"timestamp":" 947223511714"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223514847","data":{"timestamp":" 947223514846"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223517081","data":{"timestamp":" 947223517081"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223519334","data":{"timestamp":" 947223519333"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223522552","data":{"timestamp":" 947223522552"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223524775","data":{"timestamp":" 947223524775"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223526988","data":{"timestamp":" 947223526987"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223530269","data":{"timestamp":" 947223530269"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223532627","data":{"timestamp":" 947223532627"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223534988","data":{"timestamp":" 947223534987"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223538112","data":{"timestamp":" 947223538112"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223540484","data":{"timestamp":" 947223540483"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223542848","data":{"timestamp":" 947223542847"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223546253","data":{"timestamp":" 947223546252"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223546346","data":{"timestamp":" 947223546346"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223779655","data":{"timestamp":" 947223779652"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" dd011365-9fc4-4280-a8b8-2387f652b2e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223779748","data":{"timestamp":" 947223779748"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 171a3fd3-636b-4d6a-9bc0-76b3e245d838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAADUI"," userResponse":" MAADUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223785788","data":{"timestamp":" 947223785788"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 171a3fd3-636b-4d6a-9bc0-76b3e245d838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223792770","data":{"timestamp":" 947223792770"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 171a3fd3-636b-4d6a-9bc0-76b3e245d838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223797890","data":{"timestamp":" 947223797889"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 171a3fd3-636b-4d6a-9bc0-76b3e245d838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223804032","data":{"timestamp":" 947223804032"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 171a3fd3-636b-4d6a-9bc0-76b3e245d838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223810692","data":{"timestamp":" 947223810692"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 171a3fd3-636b-4d6a-9bc0-76b3e245d838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223818295","data":{"timestamp":" 947223818295"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 171a3fd3-636b-4d6a-9bc0-76b3e245d838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947223824135","data":{"timestamp":" 947223824135"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 171a3fd3-636b-4d6a-9bc0-76b3e245d838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_40","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224130618","data":{"timestamp":" 947224130612"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 171a3fd3-636b-4d6a-9bc0-76b3e245d838"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kutoka siku hiyo walikuwa maadui!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224130719","data":{"timestamp":" 947224130719"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 66f049d8-5404-4dc5-a533-379fbab91cfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAKE"," userResponse":" ZAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.show.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224136763","data":{"timestamp":" 947224136763"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 66f049d8-5404-4dc5-a533-379fbab91cfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224143254","data":{"timestamp":" 947224143253"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 66f049d8-5404-4dc5-a533-379fbab91cfc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_40"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Mtoto wa kimiujiza akala akafurahi na usiku huo akaenda zake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224154992","data":{"timestamp":" 947224154991"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DOBI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOBI"," userResponse":" DOBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224159010","data":{"timestamp":" 947224159010"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DOBI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOBI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224160578","data":{"timestamp":" 947224160577"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOGO"," userResponse":" DOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224163022","data":{"timestamp":" 947224163021"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DOGO"," userResponse":" DOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224164622","data":{"timestamp":" 947224164622"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DUMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUMA"," userResponse":" DUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224168568","data":{"timestamp":" 947224168567"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DUMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUMA"," userResponse":" DUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224170254","data":{"timestamp":" 947224170253"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DEREVA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224172901","data":{"timestamp":" 947224172900"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DEREVA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEREVA"," userResponse":" DEREVA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224174475","data":{"timestamp":" 947224174474"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DADA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224177867","data":{"timestamp":" 947224177867"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DADA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224179456","data":{"timestamp":" 947224179456"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DEBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEBE"," userResponse":" DEBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224184793","data":{"timestamp":" 947224184793"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DEBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DEBE"," userResponse":" DEBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224186413","data":{"timestamp":" 947224186413"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DAU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAU"," userResponse":" DAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224188681","data":{"timestamp":" 947224188681"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DAU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DAU"," userResponse":" DAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224190266","data":{"timestamp":" 947224190266"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DUDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUDU"," userResponse":" DUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224192395","data":{"timestamp":" 947224192395"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DUDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUDU"," userResponse":" DUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-D.rand.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224194411","data":{"timestamp":" 947224194408"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" DUDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224194517","data":{"timestamp":" 947224194517"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2fc6b3cf-3fd9-45e8-b458-1ff7664c4deb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-D.rand.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" DUDU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DUDU"," userResponse":" DUDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224234099","data":{"timestamp":" 947224234099"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224238718","data":{"timestamp":" 947224238717"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224241208","data":{"timestamp":" 947224241208"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224243530","data":{"timestamp":" 947224243530"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224293898","data":{"timestamp":" 947224293897"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224293976","data":{"timestamp":" 947224293976"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOFUATA"," userResponse":" ILIYOFUATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224307225","data":{"timestamp":" 947224307225"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224313658","data":{"timestamp":" 947224313658"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:D..D.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.34","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224321184","data":{"timestamp":" 947224321183"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224328497","data":{"timestamp":" 947224328496"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224335716","data":{"timestamp":" 947224335715"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224343495","data":{"timestamp":" 947224343495"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224351386","data":{"timestamp":" 947224351386"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224361825","data":{"timestamp":" 947224361825"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224368706","data":{"timestamp":" 947224368705"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224376120","data":{"timestamp":" 947224376120"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224382662","data":{"timestamp":" 947224382662"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224390145","data":{"timestamp":" 947224390145"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 40b0c8dd-42a7-4f52-8de5-32a3c32a41d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_36"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Alifanya vile vile siku iliyofuata."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224403574","data":{"timestamp":" 947224403574"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224403810","data":{"timestamp":" 947224403810"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224404775","data":{"timestamp":" 947224404775"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224406049","data":{"timestamp":" 947224406048"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224408996","data":{"timestamp":" 947224408995"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224409867","data":{"timestamp":" 947224409867"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224410185","data":{"timestamp":" 947224410184"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224411420","data":{"timestamp":" 947224411420"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224414978","data":{"timestamp":" 947224414969"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224415967","data":{"timestamp":" 947224415967"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224416222","data":{"timestamp":" 947224416222"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224417171","data":{"timestamp":" 947224417171"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224420007","data":{"timestamp":" 947224420007"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224421053","data":{"timestamp":" 947224421052"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224421529","data":{"timestamp":" 947224421529"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224426098","data":{"timestamp":" 947224426097"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224426202","data":{"timestamp":" 947224426202"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224432504","data":{"timestamp":" 947224432503"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224439868","data":{"timestamp":" 947224439867"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 4d0a7584-4738-4f84-b039-28625c7bf4d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_16"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224451109","data":{"timestamp":" 947224451109"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e58ef0e6-feec-4327-8cf0-661017e9ae36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224453801","data":{"timestamp":" 947224453801"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e58ef0e6-feec-4327-8cf0-661017e9ae36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ENDESHA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDESHA"," userResponse":" ENDESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224455352","data":{"timestamp":" 947224455352"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e58ef0e6-feec-4327-8cf0-661017e9ae36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" ELIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224459847","data":{"timestamp":" 947224459847"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e58ef0e6-feec-4327-8cf0-661017e9ae36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ELIMU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ELIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224461413","data":{"timestamp":" 947224461413"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e58ef0e6-feec-4327-8cf0-661017e9ae36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224466506","data":{"timestamp":" 947224466506"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e58ef0e6-feec-4327-8cf0-661017e9ae36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-E.rand.20__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224468527","data":{"timestamp":" 947224468525"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e58ef0e6-feec-4327-8cf0-661017e9ae36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224468692","data":{"timestamp":" 947224468692"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e58ef0e6-feec-4327-8cf0-661017e9ae36"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-E.rand.20__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" EMBE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224485215","data":{"timestamp":" 947224485215"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224486637","data":{"timestamp":" 947224486637"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAKUMBUKA"," userResponse":" UNAKUMBUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224487172","data":{"timestamp":" 947224487172"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224487594","data":{"timestamp":" 947224487594"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224488204","data":{"timestamp":" 947224488204"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATI"," userResponse":" KATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224488330","data":{"timestamp":" 947224488330"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224488929","data":{"timestamp":" 947224488929"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224489135","data":{"timestamp":" 947224489134"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224489824","data":{"timestamp":" 947224489821"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unakumbuka Mbio Kuu kati ya sungura na kobe?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOBE"," userResponse":" KOBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224492125","data":{"timestamp":" 947224492125"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224492604","data":{"timestamp":" 947224492604"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224493239","data":{"timestamp":" 947224493239"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224494304","data":{"timestamp":" 947224494304"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUNA"," userResponse":" HAKUNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224494960","data":{"timestamp":" 947224494960"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YEYOTE"," userResponse":" YEYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224495505","data":{"timestamp":" 947224495505"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224496227","data":{"timestamp":" 947224496227"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIKI"," userResponse":" MILIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224496293","data":{"timestamp":" 947224496293"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224497010","data":{"timestamp":" 947224497010"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224498406","data":{"timestamp":" 947224498405"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIYEWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224499241","data":{"timestamp":" 947224499241"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUONGEA"," userResponse":" KUONGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224499976","data":{"timestamp":" 947224499976"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224500112","data":{"timestamp":" 947224500111"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224500647","data":{"timestamp":" 947224500647"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JAMBO"," userResponse":" JAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224501944","data":{"timestamp":" 947224501944"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224502430","data":{"timestamp":" 947224502430"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILA"," userResponse":" ILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224503027","data":{"timestamp":" 947224503027"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILE"," userResponse":" ILE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224503649","data":{"timestamp":" 947224503648"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBIO"," userResponse":" MBIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224504064","data":{"timestamp":" 947224504064"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224504636","data":{"timestamp":" 947224504636"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224505480","data":{"timestamp":" 947224505480"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPINZANI"," userResponse":" WAPINZANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224505926","data":{"timestamp":" 947224505926"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224506544","data":{"timestamp":" 947224506544"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224526292","data":{"timestamp":" 947224526291"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224526410","data":{"timestamp":" 947224526410"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224533171","data":{"timestamp":" 947224533171"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224540841","data":{"timestamp":" 947224540840"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224547078","data":{"timestamp":" 947224547078"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224559284","data":{"timestamp":" 947224559284"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224567825","data":{"timestamp":" 947224567825"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 9d04b583-49fc-4902-93f8-4ddaf9e3f494"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_42"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kwa muda mrefu hakuna yeyote katika miliki ya wanyama aliyeweza kuongea juu ya jambo tofauti ila ile Mbio Kuu na wapinzani wake wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224578045","data":{"timestamp":" 947224578045"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILA"," userResponse":" KILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224579229","data":{"timestamp":" 947224579229"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPOMALIZA"," userResponse":" NINAPOMALIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224579824","data":{"timestamp":" 947224579824"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGA"," userResponse":" KUOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224580058","data":{"timestamp":" 947224580058"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224580501","data":{"timestamp":" 947224580501"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJI"," userResponse":" MAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224581205","data":{"timestamp":" 947224581204"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224582138","data":{"timestamp":" 947224582138"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kila ninapomaliza kuoga kwa maji moto moto."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224584436","data":{"timestamp":" 947224584436"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224584969","data":{"timestamp":" 947224584969"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224586023","data":{"timestamp":" 947224586022"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJIMAJI"," userResponse":" MAJIMAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224586636","data":{"timestamp":" 947224586635"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224587262","data":{"timestamp":" 947224587261"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224588296","data":{"timestamp":" 947224588295"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwili wangu majimaji u baridi baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224590845","data":{"timestamp":" 947224590845"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224591726","data":{"timestamp":" 947224591725"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224592198","data":{"timestamp":" 947224592198"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224593203","data":{"timestamp":" 947224593202"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224595668","data":{"timestamp":" 947224595668"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224596658","data":{"timestamp":" 947224596657"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224599838","data":{"timestamp":" 947224599838"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAZIWA"," userResponse":" MAZIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224600329","data":{"timestamp":" 947224600329"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDANI"," userResponse":" NDANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224600433","data":{"timestamp":" 947224600433"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224601142","data":{"timestamp":" 947224601141"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224602112","data":{"timestamp":" 947224602112"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224602777","data":{"timestamp":" 947224602777"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224603601","data":{"timestamp":" 947224603601"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOTO"," userResponse":" MOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224604177","data":{"timestamp":" 947224604176"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224606619","data":{"timestamp":" 947224606618"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224607088","data":{"timestamp":" 947224607087"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDE"," userResponse":" PUNDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224607561","data":{"timestamp":" 947224607561"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224608348","data":{"timestamp":" 947224608347"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224608925","data":{"timestamp":" 947224608925"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224609604","data":{"timestamp":" 947224609604"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANGU"," userResponse":" KWANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224610244","data":{"timestamp":" 947224610244"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini punde tu yako tayari kwangu kuyanywa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUYANYWA"," userResponse":" KUYANYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224612725","data":{"timestamp":" 947224612725"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224613644","data":{"timestamp":" 947224613644"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224614130","data":{"timestamp":" 947224614130"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224615134","data":{"timestamp":" 947224615134"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224617565","data":{"timestamp":" 947224617565"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224618553","data":{"timestamp":" 947224618552"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224622016","data":{"timestamp":" 947224622016"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAPAZIA"," userResponse":" MAPAZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224622093","data":{"timestamp":" 947224622093"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224623055","data":{"timestamp":" 947224623055"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MADIRISHA"," userResponse":" MADIRISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224624769","data":{"timestamp":" 947224624769"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAPAPATIKA"," userResponse":" YANAPAPATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224633991","data":{"timestamp":" 947224633991"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224634439","data":{"timestamp":" 947224634439"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224634974","data":{"timestamp":" 947224634974"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPOLE"," userResponse":" UPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224639969","data":{"timestamp":" 947224639969"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANANIPANGUSA"," userResponse":" YANANIPANGUSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224643465","data":{"timestamp":" 947224643465"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USO"," userResponse":" USO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224644000","data":{"timestamp":" 947224644000"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mapazia ya madirisha yanapapatika na kwa upole yananipangusa uso wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224646994","data":{"timestamp":" 947224646994"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224647878","data":{"timestamp":" 947224647878"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224648383","data":{"timestamp":" 947224648383"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224649440","data":{"timestamp":" 947224649440"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224651869","data":{"timestamp":" 947224651869"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224652853","data":{"timestamp":" 947224652853"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224655916","data":{"timestamp":" 947224655915"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RADI"," userResponse":" RADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224656170","data":{"timestamp":" 947224656170"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224657136","data":{"timestamp":" 947224657135"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Radi kwa umbali."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMBALI"," userResponse":" UMBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224659784","data":{"timestamp":" 947224659784"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAWINGU"," userResponse":" MAWINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224660568","data":{"timestamp":" 947224660568"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MEUSI"," userResponse":" MEUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224661752","data":{"timestamp":" 947224661752"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANASONGA"," userResponse":" YANASONGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224662348","data":{"timestamp":" 947224662348"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224662812","data":{"timestamp":" 947224662812"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mawingu meusi yanasonga upande wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANGU"," userResponse":" WANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224665219","data":{"timestamp":" 947224665218"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224666092","data":{"timestamp":" 947224666092"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224666557","data":{"timestamp":" 947224666557"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224667562","data":{"timestamp":" 947224667562"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224670114","data":{"timestamp":" 947224670114"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224671097","data":{"timestamp":" 947224671097"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224674367","data":{"timestamp":" 947224674367"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATAWI"," userResponse":" MATAWI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224675781","data":{"timestamp":" 947224675781"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAWAYAWAYA"," userResponse":" YANAWAYAWAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224676265","data":{"timestamp":" 947224676265"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224676990","data":{"timestamp":" 947224676990"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJANI"," userResponse":" MAJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224678025","data":{"timestamp":" 947224678025"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matawi yanawayawaya na majani kutetemeka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTETEMEKA"," userResponse":" KUTETEMEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224680972","data":{"timestamp":" 947224680972"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAUA"," userResponse":" MAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224682317","data":{"timestamp":" 947224682317"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANAANGUKA"," userResponse":" YANAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224682671","data":{"timestamp":" 947224682671"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224683246","data":{"timestamp":" 947224683246"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maua yanaanguka kwa upole."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPOLE"," userResponse":" UPOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224686084","data":{"timestamp":" 947224686084"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224687069","data":{"timestamp":" 947224687069"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224687564","data":{"timestamp":" 947224687564"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya yote?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YOTE"," userResponse":" YOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224690033","data":{"timestamp":" 947224690033"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224691018","data":{"timestamp":" 947224691018"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224694045","data":{"timestamp":" 947224694045"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBALI"," userResponse":" MBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224694231","data":{"timestamp":" 947224694231"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224694957","data":{"timestamp":" 947224694957"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224696283","data":{"timestamp":" 947224696282"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNACHEZA"," userResponse":" TUNACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224697598","data":{"timestamp":" 947224697598"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224698506","data":{"timestamp":" 947224698506"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAWEZA"," userResponse":" NAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224699533","data":{"timestamp":" 947224699533"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNUSIA"," userResponse":" KUNUSIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224700800","data":{"timestamp":" 947224700800"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PEREMENDE"," userResponse":" PEREMENDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224701507","data":{"timestamp":" 947224701507"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAZO"," userResponse":" AMBAZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224702024","data":{"timestamp":" 947224702024"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224703242","data":{"timestamp":" 947224703242"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbali na nyumba tunacheza lakini naweza kunusia peremende ambazo mama anatayarisha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATAYARISHA"," userResponse":" ANATAYARISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224705703","data":{"timestamp":" 947224705703"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224706592","data":{"timestamp":" 947224706592"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224707098","data":{"timestamp":" 947224707098"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224708156","data":{"timestamp":" 947224708156"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hiki kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224710583","data":{"timestamp":" 947224710583"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224711583","data":{"timestamp":" 947224711583"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224714953","data":{"timestamp":" 947224714953"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILAURI"," userResponse":" BILAURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224715451","data":{"timestamp":" 947224715451"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYO"," userResponse":" ILIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224716427","data":{"timestamp":" 947224716427"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DIRISHANI"," userResponse":" DIRISHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224717502","data":{"timestamp":" 947224717502"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAANGUKA"," userResponse":" INAANGUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224717967","data":{"timestamp":" 947224717967"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224718163","data":{"timestamp":" 947224718163"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224718982","data":{"timestamp":" 947224718981"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bilauri iliyo dirishani inaanguka chini kwa kishindo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHINDO"," userResponse":" KISHINDO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224721478","data":{"timestamp":" 947224721478"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASHUKURU"," userResponse":" NASHUKURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224722064","data":{"timestamp":" 947224722064"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUNGU"," userResponse":" MUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224723041","data":{"timestamp":" 947224723041"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKUWA"," userResponse":" SIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224723684","data":{"timestamp":" 947224723684"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nashukuru Mungu sikuwa karibu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARIBU"," userResponse":" KARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224726178","data":{"timestamp":" 947224726178"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224727024","data":{"timestamp":" 947224727024"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224727781","data":{"timestamp":" 947224727781"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKATILI"," userResponse":" UKATILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224728197","data":{"timestamp":" 947224728197"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani alifanya ukatili huu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUU"," userResponse":" HUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224730608","data":{"timestamp":" 947224730608"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224731124","data":{"timestamp":" 947224731124"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224732130","data":{"timestamp":" 947224732130"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224732395","data":{"timestamp":" 947224732394"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224733290","data":{"timestamp":" 947224733289"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka ilikuwa Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224736484","data":{"timestamp":" 947224736484"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Firimbi inapulizwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FIRIMBI"," userResponse":" FIRIMBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224737630","data":{"timestamp":" 947224737630"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Firimbi inapulizwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAPULIZWA"," userResponse":" INAPULIZWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224739895","data":{"timestamp":" 947224739895"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224740064","data":{"timestamp":" 947224740064"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224740689","data":{"timestamp":" 947224740689"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOSHI"," userResponse":" MOSHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224741626","data":{"timestamp":" 947224741626"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari la moshi linaingia."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINAINGIA"," userResponse":" LINAINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224744424","data":{"timestamp":" 947224744424"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SILIONI"," userResponse":" SILIONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224745309","data":{"timestamp":" 947224745309"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224745895","data":{"timestamp":" 947224745895"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NASIKIA"," userResponse":" NASIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224746261","data":{"timestamp":" 947224746260"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLIO"," userResponse":" MLIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224746786","data":{"timestamp":" 947224746785"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Silioni lakini nasikia mlio wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224749260","data":{"timestamp":" 947224749260"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224750140","data":{"timestamp":" 947224750140"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224750608","data":{"timestamp":" 947224750608"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224751614","data":{"timestamp":" 947224751614"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTENDEKA"," userResponse":" KUTENDEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224754082","data":{"timestamp":" 947224754082"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VAYU"," userResponse":" VAYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224755068","data":{"timestamp":" 947224755068"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Vayu upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224758946","data":{"timestamp":" 947224758946"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haionekani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAIONEKANI"," userResponse":" HAIONEKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224762047","data":{"timestamp":" 947224762047"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Haisikiki."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAISIKIKI"," userResponse":" HAISIKIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224764578","data":{"timestamp":" 947224764578"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INAFANYA"," userResponse":" INAFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224764963","data":{"timestamp":" 947224764963"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224765557","data":{"timestamp":" 947224765557"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZOTE"," userResponse":" ZOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224766303","data":{"timestamp":" 947224766303"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224766749","data":{"timestamp":" 947224766748"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Inafanya kazi zote bila neno."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NENO"," userResponse":" NENO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224769310","data":{"timestamp":" 947224769310"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAWEZA"," userResponse":" ANAWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224769735","data":{"timestamp":" 947224769735"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUWA"," userResponse":" KUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224770542","data":{"timestamp":" 947224770542"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Anaweza kuwa nani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NANI"," userResponse":" NANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224773039","data":{"timestamp":" 947224773038"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BILA"," userResponse":" BILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224773787","data":{"timestamp":" 947224773786"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Bila shaka!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHAKA"," userResponse":" SHAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224775935","data":{"timestamp":" 947224775935"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224776682","data":{"timestamp":" 947224776681"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224794699","data":{"timestamp":" 947224794695"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224794794","data":{"timestamp":" 947224794794"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPEPO"," userResponse":" UPEPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224801652","data":{"timestamp":" 947224801652"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224809611","data":{"timestamp":" 947224809611"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224817597","data":{"timestamp":" 947224817596"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" e48fe4dd-d348-432b-8fdc-7efdeaca93d6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ni upepo!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224831577","data":{"timestamp":" 947224831577"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224832462","data":{"timestamp":" 947224832462"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224833518","data":{"timestamp":" 947224833518"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224833782","data":{"timestamp":" 947224833782"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224834299","data":{"timestamp":" 947224834299"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224835137","data":{"timestamp":" 947224835136"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo awali palikuwa na panya wawili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWILI"," userResponse":" WAWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224837738","data":{"timestamp":" 947224837738"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224838302","data":{"timestamp":" 947224838302"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAO"," userResponse":" WAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224839131","data":{"timestamp":" 947224839131"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224839605","data":{"timestamp":" 947224839605"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224840280","data":{"timestamp":" 947224840280"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mmoja wao aliishi kwenye nyika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224843144","data":{"timestamp":" 947224843144"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224844018","data":{"timestamp":" 947224844018"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224844810","data":{"timestamp":" 947224844810"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224845434","data":{"timestamp":" 947224845434"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224846110","data":{"timestamp":" 947224846110"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya mwingine aliishi katika nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224849087","data":{"timestamp":" 947224849087"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224849791","data":{"timestamp":" 947224849791"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224850765","data":{"timestamp":" 947224850765"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224851829","data":{"timestamp":" 947224851829"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEISHI"," userResponse":" ALIYEISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224852474","data":{"timestamp":" 947224852474"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224853099","data":{"timestamp":" 947224853099"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224854331","data":{"timestamp":" 947224854330"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWAMBIA"," userResponse":" ALIMWAMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224854925","data":{"timestamp":" 947224854925"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224855081","data":{"timestamp":" 947224855081"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224855637","data":{"timestamp":" 947224855636"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224856842","data":{"timestamp":" 947224856842"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224858157","data":{"timestamp":" 947224858156"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224858673","data":{"timestamp":" 947224858673"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKO"," userResponse":" CHAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224859024","data":{"timestamp":" 947224859024"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SI"," userResponse":" SI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224859979","data":{"timestamp":" 947224859979"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZURI"," userResponse":" KIZURI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224861196","data":{"timestamp":" 947224861196"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224861852","data":{"timestamp":" 947224861852"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224862755","data":{"timestamp":" 947224862754"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UMEJAA"," userResponse":" UMEJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224863062","data":{"timestamp":" 947224863062"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 18"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANG"," userResponse":" MANG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224863580","data":{"timestamp":" 947224863580"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 19"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMUNG"," userResponse":" AMUNG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224864149","data":{"timestamp":" 947224864149"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 20"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMU"," userResponse":" AMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224864976","data":{"timestamp":" 947224864976"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 21"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUKU"," userResponse":" HUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224865610","data":{"timestamp":" 947224865610"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 22"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVUA"," userResponse":" MVUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224867030","data":{"timestamp":" 947224867030"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Siku moja panya aliyeishi katika nyumba alimwambia panya wa nyika wewe chakula chako si kizuri usingizi wako umejaa mang' amung' amu huku mvua ikikulowesha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 23"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIKULOWESHA"," userResponse":" IKIKULOWESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224870161","data":{"timestamp":" 947224870161"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224871055","data":{"timestamp":" 947224871055"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISI"," userResponse":" SISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224872421","data":{"timestamp":" 947224872421"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNALALA"," userResponse":" TUNALALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224873906","data":{"timestamp":" 947224873906"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOFOFO"," userResponse":" FOFOFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224875220","data":{"timestamp":" 947224875219"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224875535","data":{"timestamp":" 947224875535"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224876711","data":{"timestamp":" 947224876711"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini sisi tunalala fofofo nyumba za watemi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATEMI"," userResponse":" WATEMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224879849","data":{"timestamp":" 947224879849"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAKULA"," userResponse":" TUNAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224880818","data":{"timestamp":" 947224880817"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYAKULA"," userResponse":" VYAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224881941","data":{"timestamp":" 947224881941"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VINGI"," userResponse":" VINGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224882482","data":{"timestamp":" 947224882482"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNO"," userResponse":" MNO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224885487","data":{"timestamp":" 947224885487"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFADHALI"," userResponse":" AFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224886632","data":{"timestamp":" 947224886632"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNITEMBELEE"," userResponse":" UNITEMBELEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224887467","data":{"timestamp":" 947224887467"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224888185","data":{"timestamp":" 947224888185"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224889395","data":{"timestamp":" 947224889395"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAONE"," userResponse":" UKAONE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224890732","data":{"timestamp":" 947224890731"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAHARI"," userResponse":" FAHARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224892227","data":{"timestamp":" 947224892227"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOPO"," userResponse":" ILIYOPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224892834","data":{"timestamp":" 947224892834"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224893926","data":{"timestamp":" 947224893926"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224895338","data":{"timestamp":" 947224895337"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224895910","data":{"timestamp":" 947224895910"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224896088","data":{"timestamp":" 947224896088"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224896730","data":{"timestamp":" 947224896730"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Afadhali unitembelee siku moja ukaone fahari iliyopo wewe mwenyewe alisema panya wa nyumba."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224898903","data":{"timestamp":" 947224898903"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LEO"," userResponse":" LEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224899483","data":{"timestamp":" 947224899483"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224900159","data":{"timestamp":" 947224900159"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HII"," userResponse":" HII"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224900965","data":{"timestamp":" 947224900965"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USIKU"," userResponse":" USIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224902165","data":{"timestamp":" 947224902165"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJIBU"," userResponse":" AKAJIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224902692","data":{"timestamp":" 947224902692"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224902858","data":{"timestamp":" 947224902858"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224903465","data":{"timestamp":" 947224903464"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYIKA"," userResponse":" NYIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224905843","data":{"timestamp":" 947224905843"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKO"," userResponse":" NIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224913423","data":{"timestamp":" 947224913423"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAYARI"," userResponse":" TAYARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224913937","data":{"timestamp":" 947224913937"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224914762","data":{"timestamp":" 947224914762"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MRIJA"," userResponse":" MRIJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224915986","data":{"timestamp":" 947224915986"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAOSUBIRI"," userResponse":" UNAOSUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224917093","data":{"timestamp":" 947224917093"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Niko tayari kama mrija unaosubiri kinwaji."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINWAJI"," userResponse":" KINWAJI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224920090","data":{"timestamp":" 947224920090"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224920935","data":{"timestamp":" 947224920934"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224921389","data":{"timestamp":" 947224921389"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUO"," userResponse":" HUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224922254","data":{"timestamp":" 947224922254"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224922778","data":{"timestamp":" 947224922778"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224924183","data":{"timestamp":" 947224924183"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKASIRIKA"," userResponse":" ALIKASIRIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224925488","data":{"timestamp":" 947224925488"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AJABU"," userResponse":" AJABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224926724","data":{"timestamp":" 947224926724"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIFOKA"," userResponse":" AKIFOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224927548","data":{"timestamp":" 947224927548"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUSI"," userResponse":" MATUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224928913","data":{"timestamp":" 947224928913"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224929380","data":{"timestamp":" 947224929380"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224930220","data":{"timestamp":" 947224930220"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAOKULA"," userResponse":" WANAOKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224930738","data":{"timestamp":" 947224930737"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224931230","data":{"timestamp":" 947224931230"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHANGU"," userResponse":" CHANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224932797","data":{"timestamp":" 947224932797"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATAONA"," userResponse":" WATAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224933136","data":{"timestamp":" 947224933136"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224933735","data":{"timestamp":" 947224933735"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEMA"," userResponse":" MTEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224934604","data":{"timestamp":" 947224934604"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati huo huo mwenye nyumba alikasirika ajabu akifoka matusi panya hawa wanaokula chakula changu wataona cha mtema kuni!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 17"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNI"," userResponse":" KUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224937177","data":{"timestamp":" 947224937177"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIPO"," userResponse":" NDIPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224938623","data":{"timestamp":" 947224938622"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAWATEGEA"," userResponse":" AKAWATEGEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224939268","data":{"timestamp":" 947224939268"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" MTEGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224940364","data":{"timestamp":" 947224940364"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIYOJAA"," userResponse":" ULIYOJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224941592","data":{"timestamp":" 947224941591"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndipo akawategea mtego uliyojaa sukari."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUKARI"," userResponse":" SUKARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224944578","data":{"timestamp":" 947224944578"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224945533","data":{"timestamp":" 947224945533"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIINGIA"," userResponse":" WALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224946350","data":{"timestamp":" 947224946350"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBANI"," userResponse":" NYUMBANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224946799","data":{"timestamp":" 947224946798"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224947601","data":{"timestamp":" 947224947601"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224948509","data":{"timestamp":" 947224948508"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Panya waliingia nyumbani kula vitamu vilivyomo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VILIVYOMO"," userResponse":" VILIVYOMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224951420","data":{"timestamp":" 947224951420"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliingia wakicheka chu..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIINGIA"," userResponse":" WALIINGIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224952474","data":{"timestamp":" 947224952474"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliingia wakicheka chu..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKICHEKA"," userResponse":" WAKICHEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224953323","data":{"timestamp":" 947224953323"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Waliingia wakicheka chu..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHU"," userResponse":" CHU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224957947","data":{"timestamp":" 947224957947"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOUFIKIA"," userResponse":" WALIPOUFIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224958643","data":{"timestamp":" 947224958643"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTEGO"," userResponse":" MTEGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224959493","data":{"timestamp":" 947224959492"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224959667","data":{"timestamp":" 947224959667"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224960177","data":{"timestamp":" 947224960177"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMBA"," userResponse":" NYUMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224961160","data":{"timestamp":" 947224961160"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISEMA"," userResponse":" ALISEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224962454","data":{"timestamp":" 947224962454"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WACHA"," userResponse":" WACHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224963191","data":{"timestamp":" 947224963190"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIONJE"," userResponse":" NIONJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224963996","data":{"timestamp":" 947224963996"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipoufikia mtego panya wa nyumba alisema wacha nionje sukari ..."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUKARI"," userResponse":" SUKARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224967088","data":{"timestamp":" 947224967088"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAZAMA"," userResponse":" TAZAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224967684","data":{"timestamp":" 947224967684"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224968346","data":{"timestamp":" 947224968346"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITAMU"," userResponse":" VITAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224969292","data":{"timestamp":" 947224969291"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUNAVYOKULA"," userResponse":" TUNAVYOKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224969756","data":{"timestamp":" 947224969756"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tazama vitamu vitamu tunavyokula hapa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224972855","data":{"timestamp":" 947224972855"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224973450","data":{"timestamp":" 947224973450"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABLA"," userResponse":" KABLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224974013","data":{"timestamp":" 947224974013"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224981830","data":{"timestamp":" 947224981830"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAJAPATA"," userResponse":" HAJAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_45","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224981851","data":{"timestamp":" 947224981851"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224981973","data":{"timestamp":" 947224981973"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAJAPATA"," userResponse":" HAJAPATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947224991092","data":{"timestamp":" 947224991092"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225001463","data":{"timestamp":" 947225001461"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:E..E.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225009966","data":{"timestamp":" 947225009966"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225112345","data":{"timestamp":" 947225112344"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 35de2eb7-9c87-4318-b615-7da8622a6994"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_45"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Lakini kabla panya hajapata kugusa sukari mtego ukamnasa kichwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225112536","data":{"timestamp":" 947225112536"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 97d08fb3-15c2-4379-89c7-095090eeada1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MILIMA"," userResponse":" MILIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225120119","data":{"timestamp":" 947225120119"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 97d08fb3-15c2-4379-89c7-095090eeada1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:1..4.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225129694","data":{"timestamp":" 947225129694"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 97d08fb3-15c2-4379-89c7-095090eeada1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225137701","data":{"timestamp":" 947225137701"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 97d08fb3-15c2-4379-89c7-095090eeada1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225209626","data":{"timestamp":" 947225209626"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 97d08fb3-15c2-4379-89c7-095090eeada1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_41"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Miti ilimea kwenye mitelemko ya milima."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225209746","data":{"timestamp":" 947225209746"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ead2b599-4b08-4e36-b90b-8bf804ccfed8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYEWE"," userResponse":" MWENYEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225217204","data":{"timestamp":" 947225217203"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ead2b599-4b08-4e36-b90b-8bf804ccfed8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225235970","data":{"timestamp":" 947225235970"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ead2b599-4b08-4e36-b90b-8bf804ccfed8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225245905","data":{"timestamp":" 947225245905"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ead2b599-4b08-4e36-b90b-8bf804ccfed8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225260094","data":{"timestamp":" 947225260093"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ead2b599-4b08-4e36-b90b-8bf804ccfed8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225266460","data":{"timestamp":" 947225266459"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ead2b599-4b08-4e36-b90b-8bf804ccfed8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.gen.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225276230","data":{"timestamp":" 947225276230"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" ead2b599-4b08-4e36-b90b-8bf804ccfed8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.gen.hear__story_43"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Naweza kutulia na kukifurahia kitabu mimi mwenyewe!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225286310","data":{"timestamp":" 947225286310"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225294421","data":{"timestamp":" 947225294420"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225294423","data":{"timestamp":" 947225294423"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225294544","data":{"timestamp":" 947225294544"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225312265","data":{"timestamp":" 947225312265"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.show.37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225319366","data":{"timestamp":" 947225319366"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_17","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225333289","data":{"timestamp":" 947225333289"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225352460","data":{"timestamp":" 947225352460"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.mc.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225362318","data":{"timestamp":" 947225362317"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:F..F.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.38","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225373387","data":{"timestamp":" 947225373386"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225382362","data":{"timestamp":" 947225382362"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225391719","data":{"timestamp":" 947225391718"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.asc.q2s.AV.rise.14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225401644","data":{"timestamp":" 947225401644"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225411044","data":{"timestamp":" 947225411043"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225420228","data":{"timestamp":" 947225420222"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225431446","data":{"timestamp":" 947225431446"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.dn.q2s.AV.mc.23","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225441442","data":{"timestamp":" 947225441441"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225450476","data":{"timestamp":" 947225450476"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225462563","data":{"timestamp":" 947225462563"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:G..G.all.rand.all.stat.show.39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947225473764","data":{"timestamp":" 947225473763"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_082735"," gameId":" 2847b4a5-c904-49c0-8512-c694797f158b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}